Collins Ukpabi

Community worker

Address: 1 Chaucer Street, Sydenham, Christchurch 8023

Mobile: (64) 022 651 5707 E-mail: ukpabicc@gmail.com

Resume Summary

Over 12 months experience in community service work. I have over 12 months experience in the power generation and the energy industry and experience in Information and Communication Technologies (ICT). My main strength is in IT technical support which enables me to apply my natural problem-detection and passion for solving problems particularly of a technical nature full potentials. I am looking forward to leveraging this potential in the fast growing ICT industry.

Education

2016-06 to 2017-05 **Certificate of Enrolment in Doctor of Philosophy** – (PROGRAM NOT COMPLETED)

2016-11 to 2017-12 **New Zealand Certificate in Health and Wellbeing Careerforce, New Zealand** (Private Training Establishment)

2013- 02 to 2014-07 **Master of Management Information Systems Cyprus International University**

2001-01 to 2009-01 **Bachelor of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering** University of Port Harcourt

1994-01 to 2000-06 **West African Senior School Certificate Luwasa High School**

1988 – 1993 First School Leaving Certificate NEPA Staff Primary School

Work Experience

2016-09 to Present

Community Service (Community Support Worker)

Brackenridge Estate Limited, New Zealand

- Supporting clients to make choices and developing plans for community participation
- Meeting with clients/family/advocate/representatives and relevant stakeholders to assess and discuss their progress and problems/difficulties
- Maintaining contact with Healthcare providers and other social service agencies
- Providing personal care, physical and emotional support to clients

2016-03 to 2016-05

IT/Strategy development and Compliance

Exinno White Consults, Nigeria

- Managing hardware and software to meet organisation's requirements
- Communicating with staff and management to enhance effective use of IT resources
- Using fundamentals of information System concepts and practice to support organisational procedures and systems
- Installing and configuring hardware for specific organisational needs

2014-08 to 2016-05

Secondary School Teacher (Physics, Trade and Basic science teacher)

High-Lead Comprehensive College, Nigeria

- Planning and preparing lessons according to State approved curriculum
- Teaching using subject resources using appropriate systematic methodologies
- Assessing students and correcting assignments and tests and discussing results with parents
- Maintaining scholastic records
- Attending educational conferences, training workshops and staff meetings

2011-02 to 2012-06

Mechanical Engineering Technician (Mechanical Operator/Technician)

Negris Limited, Nigeria

- Plant engineer on remote site- Operations, Engineering and Maintenance (OEM)
- Installation, repair and maintenance of power equipment and auxiliaries
- Carrying out mechanical tests and troubleshooting generator and auxiliaries

• Reporting system operating performance parameters TEM screen to supervisor and onward decision-making for loading, start-up/shut-downs as required

2009-07 to 2010-07

Youth Worker

National Youth Service Corps, Nigeria

- Assisting local schools with teaching services
- Providing referrals to social services
- Assisting community in local services and activities
- Counselling students on career choices, financial and family problems

Certificates and Certificate of Attendance

- Fire Evacuation and Extinguisher Training 2017
- Understanding Cultural Diversity and Cultural safety November, 2016
- Comprehensive First Aid 2016
- Educational Development 2015

Skills

Windows and operational knowledge of networking
Basic IT technical support
Installation and configuring hardware and software installation and configuration
Operation, Engineering and Maintenance
Communication, Personal and interpersonal skills
Team working
Problem-solving
Project management

References provided upon request